Experimental College Records UA044
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Explorations and Perspectives, 1967 -- 2000; UA044.002; 6.75 Linear Feet
  - Freshman Exploration "TV Sitcoms" Fall, 1985; UA044.002.006.00026 (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 A Spr, 1986; UA044.002.006.00027; Bartholet, Ann; Ramirez, Ishmael (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 B Spr, 1986; UA044.002.006.00028; Greenberg, Cara; McCann, Molly (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 C Spr, 1986; UA044.002.006.00029; Chapin, Matthew; Hirsch, Lisa; Petterson, Bettina (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 D Spr, 1986; UA044.002.006.00030; Pournaras, Alexandra; Welch, Megan (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 N: Men/Women: Changing Times/Roles F, 1986; UA044.002.006.00031; Pidedjian, Datev; Reale, Rosario; Hwang, Diana (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 P Studies In Human Relationships F, 1986; UA044.002.006.00032; Bramberg, Cheryl; Perlow, Julie; Rodman, Lisa (Box 6)
  - EXP F 86 Creative Thinking, 1986; UA044.002.006.00033; Hirsch, Emily; Wong, Linda (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 R F86 Creative Thinking, 1986; UA044.002.006.00034; Putnoi, Deborah; Van Pelt, Elizabeth (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 S F86 Creative Thinking/ Decision Making, 1986; UA044.002.006.00035; Putnoi, Deborah; Van Pelt, Elizabeth (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 T F86 The Games People Play, 1986; UA044.002.006.00036; Kaplan, Tracey; Nataupsky, Steven (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 U Everything's Choices, 1986; UA044.002.006.00037; Herman, Rachel; Klinger, Michele (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 V F86 Rack Your Brain, 1986; UA044.002.006.00038; Heilbraun, Jeff; Sessler, Nina E.; Smick, Deborah R. (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 W F86 Through the Eyes of a Child, 1986; UA044.002.006.00039; Leone, John; Tanner, Robyne (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 X F86 An Edifice Complex, 1986; UA044.002.006.00040; Cohen, Jill; Michel, Jeffrey (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 Y F86 Beauty in Eye of Beholder, 1986; UA044.002.006.00041; Hernandez, Jacquie; McKittrick, Charlie; Scali, Marisa (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 Z F86 Culture Today, 1986; UA044.002.006.00042; George, William; Sloan, Katie (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 AA F86 Top 40 Classical, 1986; UA044.002.006.00043; Goldfischer, Evan; Shefts, Susan (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 BB F86 Rock Music- Elvis P to Elvis C, 1986; UA044.002.006.00044 (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 CC F86 Journalism, 1986; UA044.002.006.00045; Newman, Jon; Peltz, Carol (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 DD F86 Works and Philos of Woody Allen, 1986; UA044.002.006.00046; Eckhouse, D. Noah; Koppelman, Brian (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 EE F86 Comedies of America, 1986; UA044.002.006.00047; Abbate, Edith; Levitt, Debra; Tennenbaum, Michael (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 FF F86 Film-Mirror of American Society, 1986; UA044.002.006.00048; Alfieri, Paul; Depillis, Mark; Edelstein, Carrie (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 GG F86 Alfred Hitchcock, 1986; UA044.002.006.00049; Eskenazi, David; Saxe, John (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 HH F86 Superheroes, 1986; UA044.002.006.00050; Blumenfeld, Jill; Flax, Susie; Joseph, Daniel (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 HH F86 Vietnam and Film, 1986; UA044.002.006.00051; Stupp, Steven; Wasserman, Jason (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 KK F86 War's Representation in Film, 1986; UA044.002.006.00052; Cohen, Bonni; Cudahy, Dan (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 LL F86 The Kennedy Era, 1986; UA044.002.006.00053; Hellman, Greg; Maslin, Kirsten (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 MM F86 America 1950s/1980s, 1986; UA044.002.006.00054; Manassee, Mark; Meyer, Andrew (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 NN F86 Zen and the Art of America, 1986; UA044.002.006.00055; Grekin, Peter; Kirsch, Vanessa; MacMillan, Rob (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 PP F86 Realms of Social Influence in America, 1986; UA044.002.006.00056; Britman, Susan; Langbein, Stuart; Livitz, Stacy (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 QQ F86 Intro to Finance and Investment, 1986; UA044.002.006.00057; Cohen, Jeffrey; Sachs, David (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 RR F86 Facing the Fitness Fad, 1986; UA044.002.006.00058; Friedman, Rachel; Glazer, Deborah; Seligman, Marcy (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 SS F86 Nutrition for Ourselves/Others, 1986; UA044.002.006.00059; Balick, Dana; Harbour, Allison (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 TT F86 You Are What You Eat, 1986; UA044.002.006.00060; Miller, Karen; Weinberg, Susan (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 UU F86 Sports Issues, 1986; UA044.002.006.00061; Brenan, Margaret; Parven, Andrew; Stein, Gerald (Box 6)
  - Explorations Fall, 1986; UA044.002.006.00062 (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 A F86 Right When You Get There, 1986; UA044.002.006.00063; Graham, Sally Ann; Perel, Dana (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 B F86 Relationships, 1986; UA044.002.006.00064; Eiselman, Amy; Pellecchia, Michael (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 C F86 It's Your Move, 1986; UA044.002.006.00065; Heiman, Julie; Jacobs, Lisa; Rando, Joe (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 D F86 Coming of Age at College, 1986; UA044.002.006.00066; Bortman, Scott; Denaro, Christine; Greengrass, Scott (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 E F86 Adolescence: A Tricky Transition, 1986; UA044.002.006.00067; Bowen, Steve; Hoogendoorn, Ingrid; Latts, Susan (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 F F86 Adolescence Through Film/Music/Lit, 1986; UA044.002.006.00068; Berrafati, Linda; Cipro, Brian; Geller, Russell (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 G F86 Here's Looking at You Kid, 1986; UA044.002.006.00069; Cherry, Jessica; Thurm, Wendy (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 J F86 Issues of the 80s, 1986; UA044.002.006.00070; Bronfman, Matt; Smilow, Marni; Stone, David (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 H F86 Issues of Identity and Self, 1986; UA044.002.006.00071; Higgins, Elizabeth; Werger, Melissa (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 K F86 Contemporary Issues on Campus, 1986; UA044.002.006.00072; O'Toole, John; Salloway, Leslie (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 L F86 Coming Together; Blacks/Jews, 1986; UA044.002.006.00073; Brown, Daniel; Kotzen, Andrew; Vega, Eliza (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 M F86 To Be Young/Gifted/Black, 1986; UA044.002.006.00074; Eubanks, Catherine; Robinson, Bryant (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 VV F86 More Than Just a Game, 1986; UA044.002.006.00075; Lippert, Michael; Saltzman, Lenny (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 WW F86 Sports in Education, 1986; UA044.002.006.00076; Bunnell, Tim; Silverman, Beth; Swain, Linda (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 XX F86 Hard Sell In The Media, 1986; UA044.002.006.00077; Nixon, Cheryl; Predham, Lorraine; Willner, Michael (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 YY F86 Made You Look!, 1986; UA044.002.006.00078; London, Jacqueline; Stevens, Eric (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 ZZ F86 Ads, We Love To Hate Them, 1986; UA044.002.006.00079; Intravaia, Diane; Lombardo, Lois; Rosenberg, Rachel (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 AZ F86 Ads, Madison Avenue Goes Abroad, 1986; UA044.002.006.00080; Marcus, Dianne; Rauch, Amanda (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 BZ F86 How To Get What You Want!, 1986; UA044.002.006.00081; Markus, David; Monagle, Christine (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 CZ F86 Concerning Ourselves, 1986; UA044.002.006.00082; Finkelman, David; Rosenberg, Amy; Rose, Alysa (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 DZ F86 Snapshots of Boston, 1986; UA044.002.006.00083; Newton, Alison; Rudnick, Barbara (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 EZ F86 Human Rights/Western Liberal Tradition, 1986; UA044.002.006.00084; Swartz, Amy; Harberg, David (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 FZ F86 Through Star Spangled Glasses, 1986; UA044.002.006.00085; Davila, Arlene; Panas, Jennifer; Schwartz, Jordan (Box 6)
  - Sports Psychology, 1986; UA044.002.006.00086; Cheren, Stephen; Kraft, Dan; Leven, Jon (Box 6)
  - Gastronomy, 1986; UA044.002.006.00087; Kubba, Janan; Spanninga, Maatje (Box 6)
  - Activism Without Acid, 1986; UA044.002.006.00088; DeRochi, Andrea (Box 6)
  - War Poetry and Song, 1986; UA044.002.006.00089; Braitman, Blanche; Nelligan, Mary Beth (Box 6)
  - Welcome to the College Experience, 1986; UA044.002.006.00090; Gratiano, Karen; Milman, Elizabeth (Box 6)
  - Horses And Their Role In Society, 1986; UA044.002.006.00091; Wylde, Peter; Robles, Esther; Dicker, Randi (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 A Spring, 1986; UA044.002.006.00092; Russell, Richard; Salvato, Annette (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 B Spring, 1987; UA044.002.006.00093; Boynton, Meghan; Doyle, Patrick (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 C Spring, 1987; UA044.002.006.00094; O'Riordan, Siobhan; Johnson, Priscilla (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 D Spring, 1987; UA044.002.006.00095; Adams, Ben; Glick, Andrew (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 E Spring, 1987; UA044.002.006.00096; Lance, Kate; Hare, Kirstina (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 F Spring, 1987; UA044.002.006.00097; Karlin, Linda; Marcus, Debbie (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 G Spring, 1987; UA044.002.006.00098; Brady, Lynn; Kemp, Katie; Wilcox, Cecilia (Box 6)
  - Indepency/ Dependency Throughout the Life Cycle, 1987; UA044.002.006.00099; Quelch, Sheryl J.; Regan, Jennifer (Box 6)
  - What's the Scoop, 1987; UA044.002.006.00100; Miller, Jennifer; Jacobs, Jeffrey (Box 6)
  - Alone In The Crowd, 1985; UA044.002.006.00101; Larsen, Jonathon; Brenman, Mark (Box 6)
  - Politics and the Mass Media, 1985; UA044.002.006.00102; Lee, Vivian; Shelby, Karen (Box 6)
  - Women in the Third World, 1985; UA044.002.006.00103; de Silva, Shyami; Uppal, Jyotsana (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 A F87 Issues on College Campuses, 1987; UA044.002.006.00104; Kaplan, Meredith; Barror, Sean; Lake, Rhonda (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 B F87 Dynamics of Relationships, 1987; UA044.002.006.00105; Cihak, Kristin; Page, Karen; Swicker, Stefan (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 C F87 Family Ties, 1987; UA044.002.006.00106; Pass, Susan; Zelma, Alysa (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 D F87 Decision Making, 1987; UA044.002.006.00107; Bishop, Alisa; Duncan, Anne; Kaplan, Rachel (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 E F87 Decision Making Why Do DO It?, 1987; UA044.002.006.00108; Blackman, Laura; Ferrarese, Paul; Ostroff, Steve (Box 6)
  - EXP 009 F Fall 1987 Solitude and Community, UA044.002.007.00001; Autor, David H.; Mountjoy, Alex; Zambelli, Jean (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 G Fall 1987 Relationships, UA044.002.007.00002; Pachman, Andrew; Stern, Andrew (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 H F87 Is What You Say What You Mean?, 1987; UA044.002.007.00003; Schultz, Michael; Breslow, Sherry (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 J F87 Student Activism 60s-80s, 1987; UA044.002.007.00004; Cadet, Carlo; Ganz, Jeffrey; Radcliffe, Lisa (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 L F87 Teens Through The Decades, 1987; UA044.002.007.00005; Freedman, Deborah; Mirsky, Brett (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 M F87 Teens Through The Ages, 1987; UA044.002.007.00006; Gerber, Robin; Goodman, Marc; Leventhal,Eve (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 N F87 Heroes In American Culture, 1987; UA044.002.007.00007; Ashley, Jonathan; Katz, John; Traum, Jeff (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 P F87 American Culture in 70s-80s, 1987; UA044.002.007.00008; Epstein, Michael; Gladstone, Larry (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 Q F87 Sterotypes In Pop Culture, 1987; UA044.002.007.00009; Keenan, Patrick; Mankiewicz, Benjamin; Ryan, William F. (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 R F87 Differences Across America, 1987; UA044.002.007.00010; Keenan, Patrick; Mankiewicz, Benjamin; Ryan, William F. (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 S F87 Combatting Discrimination, 1987; UA044.002.007.00011; Block, Debbie; Bockman, Nicole; Neal, David (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 T F87 Music and Religion, 1987; UA044.002.007.00012; Mahler, Nancy; Wiley, David (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 U F87 Catholicism in the Eighties, 1987; UA044.002.007.00013; Kimball, Paulette; Wallace, Leslie (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 V F87 Political and Cultural History of Boston, 1987; UA044.002.007.00014; Gorecki, Meg; Meyer, Daniel (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 W F87 Beyond Apple Pie, 1987; UA044.002.007.00015; Hahn, Tracy; Grise, Mark; Rosen, Janet (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 X F87 Portrayal of Racial Minority, 1987; UA044.002.007.00016; Johns, Karen; Sterghos, Nicole; Woolever, Raj (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 Y F87 A Sign of the Times, 1987; UA044.002.007.00017; Katz, Eric; Petrillo, Louis (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 Z F87 More than Movies, 1987; UA044.002.007.00018; Dunn, Peter; Greenberg, Michael (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 AA F87 Discovery of Africa Through Video, 1987; UA044.002.007.00019; Mboa, Suzan; Shoyinka, Lola; Terry, Orlinka (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 BB F87 From Kahn To O'Connor, 1987; UA044.002.007.00020; Reinke, Janet; Goldberg, Susan (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 CC F87 G'Day Mate, 1987; UA044.002.007.00021; Falcone, Ian; Falzarano, Anne; Shrager, Adam (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 DD F87 The Culture Gap, 1987; UA044.002.007.00022; Finegan, Corinne; Dumouchel, Kristen; Weinstock, Jennifer (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 EE F87 Horror in Western Literature, 1987; UA044.002.007.00023; Golden, Christopher; Schwartz, Alex (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 FF F87 It's Not Whether You Win Or Lose, 1987; UA044.002.007.00024; Callahan, Stephen; Salzman, Cindy; Kluznick, Daniel (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 GG F87 Competition -Friend or Foe?, 1987; UA044.002.007.00025; Callahan, Stephen; Salzman, Cindy; Kluznick, Daniel (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 HH F87 College Athetics, 1987; UA044.002.007.00026; Lieberman, Neil; Sternheim, Sabrina; Zambell, Jay (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 JJ F87 Inside Sports, 1987; UA044.002.007.00027; Horgan, P.J.; Leven, Jon; Kabakow, James (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 KK F87 Sound Mind, Sound Body, 1987; UA044.002.007.00028; Jacobowitz, Dana; Jacobson, Larry; Segel, Steve (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 LL F87 Mcdonalds, Tofu, and You, 1987; UA044.002.007.00029; Heney, Steve; Vlahakis, Alisa (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 MM 87 Sexual Awareness, 1987; UA044.002.007.00030; Giroux, Noelle; Sloane, Michael; Stults, Virginia (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 NN 87 Health and Sexuality, 1987; UA044.002.007.00031; Masheb, Robin; Radding, Jennifer; Romaniello, Steve (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 PP 87 What is Mathematics?, 1987; UA044.002.007.00032; Cassidy, Daniel; Daver, Tannaz (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 ZZ MASH in Society, 1987; UA044.002.007.00033; Giller, Ron; Grouit, Philip; Seldin, Mike (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 AZ The University and The Student, 1987; UA044.002.007.00034; Baturin, Lisa; Lodi, Maria (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 AZ Comics and American Culture, 1987; UA044.002.007.00035; Bavarn, Stephanie; Gerber, Michael (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 CZ Financial Markets, 1987; UA044.002.007.00036; Kaplan, Karen; Walker, Jennifer (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 QQ Financial Markets, 1987; UA044.002.007.00037; Konecky, Chad; Langsam, Jessica; Stern, Andrew (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 RR Advertising-Information, Persuasion, Deception, 1987; UA044.002.007.00038; Gelman, Melissa; Palmer, Laura; Wolfe, Allison (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 SS F'87 Advertising- Catch the Wave, 1987; UA044.002.007.00039; Brodeur, Christine; Boermeester, Kiera; O'Neil, Danny (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 TT F'87 Comedy and Its Social Relevance, 1987; UA044.002.007.00040; Perlow, Julie; Reich, Julie (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 UU F'87 Everyone's a Comedian, 1987; UA044.002.007.00041; Albenberg, David; Volman, Josef (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 VV F'87 Comedy As You Like It, 1987; UA044.002.007.00042; Alvarado, Julie; D'Avanzo, Louis; Nicholas, Matthew (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 XX F87 Comedy in the 20th Century, 1987; UA044.002.007.00043; Floch, Neil; Hermann, Philip; Marguiles, Brian (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 WW F87 Appreciating American Comedy, 1987; UA044.002.007.00044; Abrams, Jennifer; Brendler, Tom (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 YY F87 Woody Allen: First 50 Years, 1987; UA044.002.007.00045; Lickstein, David; Locke, Steven; Rogelberg, Steven (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 T F88 Science Fiction and Fantasy, 1988; UA044.002.007.00046; Kaminstein, Ann; Phetteplace, Susan (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 U F88 Chills, Thrills, and Things That Go Bump in the Night, 1988; UA044.002.007.00047; Fittipaldi, Nancy; Kellstedt, Perry (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 V F88 Alfred Hitchcock-The Man and His Films, 1988; UA044.002.007.00048; Obermeier, Andrew; Ali, Mohamed (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 W F88 The Art of Woody Allen, 1988; UA044.002.007.00049; Zucker, Scott; Cohen, Michael (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 X F88 Beyond Bugs Bunny, 1988; UA044.002.007.00050; Bramwit, Mark; Perlitsh, Suzanne (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 Y F88 American Crafts, 1988; UA044.002.007.00051; Cunningham, Sarah; Clayton, Anthony (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 Z F88 Broadway Unbound-The Musical and American Society, 1988; UA044.002.007.00052; Bruce, Garnett; Geesey, Katherine (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 AA F88 Music and Emotion, 1988; UA044.002.007.00053; Chodroff, Marci; Emond, Dawn-Marie (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 BB F88 Order in Chaos, 1988; UA044.002.007.00054; Reyna, David; Dickstein, David (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 CC F88 The Psychology of Drugs, 1988; UA044.002.007.00055; Heyman, Joanne; Frauwirth, Stacy (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 DD F88 Drugs- All Sides of the Story, 1988; UA044.002.007.00056; Pruzan, Jonathan; Roth, Marjorie (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 EE F88 Nutrition and Health in the '80's, 1988; UA044.002.007.00057; Siben, Sharon; Mussman, Laurie (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 FF F88 Contemporary Issues in Health and Fitness, 1988; UA044.002.007.00058; Schneider, Lisa; Caplan, Jodi (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 GG F88 Sports and Social Realities, 1988; UA044.002.007.00059; Lipton, Michael; Sacks, Eric (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 A F88 The Changing American Family, 1988; UA044.002.007.00060; Flaherty, Michael-Kelly; Meyers, Beth (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 B F88 From Bobby Socks to Reeboks-Teenagers through the Decades, 1988; UA044.002.007.00061; Edinburg, Barry; Doppelt, Michael (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 C F88 Rattles to Wrinkles-Aging in America, 1988; UA044.002.007.00062; Jordan, Scott; Jacobs, Anne (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 D F88 Confronting Stereotypes-Prejudice and Fear in America, 1988; UA044.002.007.00063; Yu, Danny; McKinnon, Tanya (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 E F88 Community Relations and Life at Tufts, 1988; UA044.002.007.00064; Murphy, Edward; DeGeorge, Janine (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 F F88 Rightwing Extremists in America, 1988; UA044.002.007.00065; Buchman, Laura; Granat, Cary (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 G F88 We All Want to Change the World and Some of Us Do, 1988; UA044.002.007.00066; Eckhaus, Stephanie; Marshall, Kim (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 H F88 Moral Dilemmas, 1988; UA044.002.007.00067; Martin, Romy; Levy, Allison (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 J F88 You Decide, 1988; UA044.002.007.00068; Romeo, Marianne; Jalelian, Lincoln (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 K F88 Boesky, Biden, Bakker and Beyond- Ethics in the 1980's, 1988; UA044.002.007.00069; Novick, Scott; Schickler, Lauren (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 L F88 Radical America-A Historical Perspective, 1988; UA044.002.007.00070; Smith, Nina; Tittemore, Lisa (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 M F88 Boston-Politics, Ethnicity and Immigration, 1988; UA044.002.007.00071; Collier, Charles; Petersen, Timothy (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 N F88 Vietnam-The Experience and Its Impact, 1988; UA044.002.007.00072; Berrafati, Joseph; Miller, James (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 P F88 Political Culture-The United States and the Soviet Union, 1988; UA044.002.007.00073; Polack, Marina; Muster, Lynn (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 Q F88 Propaganda, Politics and Advertising, 1988; UA044.002.007.00074; Cohen, Scott; Harrison, Rodney (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 R F88 Campaign '88-Behind the Scenes, 1988; UA044.002.007.00075; Steckler, Bruce; Krinzman, Melissa (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 S F88 Science Fiction-Visions of the Future, 1988; UA044.002.007.00076; Moss, Debra; Simon, Michael (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 H F89 You, Me, Us and Them-Dynamics of Group Relationships, 1989; UA044.002.007.00077; Baglieri, Christopher; Katz, Alicia (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 J F89 Fraternity/Sorority-Changing Character of Greek Life, 1989; UA044.002.007.00078; Schlein, Jennifer; Charnes, Stacey (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 K F89 Ciao Italia!, 1989; UA044.002.007.00079; Greene, Samantha; Neuthaler, Mindy (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 L F89 African-Americans: History, Politics and Culture, 1989; UA044.002.007.00080; Frazier, Myra; Yudell, Michael (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 M F89 Religion and the State-U.S. and World Perspective, 1989; UA044.002.007.00081; Reed, Katherine; Kuo, J. David (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 N F89 Issues in Animal Exploitation, 1989; UA044.002.007.00082; Gianetti, Pamela; Murin, Susan (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 Q F89 Woody Allen Through the Years, 1989; UA044.002.007.00083; Sorokin, Lisa; Seftel, Joshua (Box 7)
  - EXP 009 R F89 Laughing Matters-Comedy in Serious Business, 1989; UA044.002.007.00084; Gal, Peter; Rickards, Jennifer (Box 7)
  - EXP 008 S F, 1989; UA044.002.008.00001; Ford, Mary C.; Ligorsky, Brenda (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 T F, 1989; UA044.002.008.00002; Erekson, Melissa; McCasland, Barry (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 U F, 1989; UA044.002.008.00003; Lindo, Marjorie F.; Ricci, Elizabeth R. (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 V F, 1989; UA044.002.008.00004; Ansell, Margaret; Roth, Marjorie (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 W F, 1989; UA044.002.008.00005; Sharon, Joanne; Walker, Robin K. (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 X F, 1989; UA044.002.008.00006; Simmons, Justine; Stewart, Jeffrey (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 Y F, 1989; UA044.002.008.00007; Griffey, Anita Y.; Manning, Lisa M. (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 P F, 1989; UA044.002.008.00008; Griffey, Anita Y. (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 A F, 1989; UA044.002.008.00009; Bertasi, Jamie; Tinger, John (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 Q F, 1989; UA044.002.008.00010; Hamilton, David; Ketcham, Sam (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 B F, 1989; UA044.002.008.00011; Bergman, Andrew; Dockser, Pamela (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 C F, 1989; UA044.002.008.00012; Donahue, Kimberly Beth; Manyin, Mark (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 D F, 1989; UA044.002.008.00013; Chokroverty, Linda; Drob, Joey (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 E F, 1989; UA044.002.008.00014; Dick, Morna Elizabeth; Keller, Rebecca E. (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 F F, 1989; UA044.002.008.00015; Brown, Jeff; Leong, Melinda (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 G F, 1989; UA044.002.008.00016; Brady, Julia M.; Block, Lisa (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 H F, 1989; UA044.002.008.00017; Kerker, Bonnie; Pechman, Leslie (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 J F, 1989; UA044.002.008.00018; Edidin, Laura; Jacobson, William B. (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 K F, 1989; UA044.002.008.00019; Fitzgerald, Kathleen; Sadlier, Mary (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 M F, 1989; UA044.002.008.00020; Glazer, Daryl F.; LeFave, Suzanne H. (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 N F, 1989; UA044.002.008.00021; Marin, Julie; Grant, Sandi (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 R F, 1989; UA044.002.008.00022; Lee, Erika; Lewis, Raphael (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 CC F'89 The Health Care Dilemma, 1989; UA044.002.008.00023; Flaherty, Sean; Weiner, Jocelyn (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 DD F'89 Drugs-The Inside Story, 1989; UA044.002.008.00024; Frauwirth, Stacy; Heyman, Joanne (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 EE F'89 Sound Mind, Sound Body, 1989; UA044.002.008.00025; Gatcliffe, Troy; Muchin, Suzanne (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 FF F'89 Boston in the Twentieth Century, 1989; UA044.002.008.00026; Ingerman, Brett; Nelson Jones, Julie (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 GG F'89 Neighborhoods of Boston, 1989; UA044.002.008.00027; Weston, Melanie; Wolfe, Brent (Box 8)
  - EXP 008 HH F'89 Boston-Small City Turned Metropolis, 1989; UA044.002.008.00028; Klaris, Joshua J.; Sonder, Claudia (Box 8)
  - EXP 009 S F'89 The Cinema of Hitchcock, 1989; UA044.002.008.00029 (Box 8)
  - EXP 009 T F'89 The Development of the Horror Genre, 1989; UA044.002.008.00030; Fittipaldi, Nancy; Kellstedt, Perry (Box 8)
  - EXP 009 U F'89 Explanations for the Unexplained, 1989; UA044.002.008.00031; Karetnick, Jennifer; Rosenthal, Ann (Box 8)
  - EXP 009 V F'89 A Feast of Horror-The Novels of Stephen King, 1989; UA044.002.008.00032; Frank, Bradley; Bluth, Jamie (Box 8)
  - EXP 009 W F'89 Forgotten Voices, 1989; UA044.002.008.00033; Allingham, Liesl; O'Driscoll, Bridget (Box 8)
  - EXP 009 X F'89 The Mysteries of Agatha Christie, 1989; UA044.002.008.00034; Gottovi, Sara; Lewiss, Peter (Box 8)
  - EXP 009 Y F'89 Musical Improvisation, 1989; UA044.002.008.00035; Sigman, Jonathan; Waldheger, Gavin (Box 8)
  - EXP 009 Z F'89 To Create-Art and the Artistic Conscience, 1989; UA044.002.008.00036; McCauley, Kevin; Cunningham, Sarah (Box 8)
  - EXP 009 AA F'89 Financial Markets-Clashes, Controversies and Culture, 1989; UA044.002.008.00037; Chow, Kendrick; Goldberg, Adam (Box 8)
  - EXP 009 BB F'89 Mind Over Body?, 1989; UA044.002.009.00001; Lazar, Cindy; Miller, Abby (Box 9)
  - EXP 009 A F'89 Contemporary American Family, 1989; UA044.002.009.00002; Blanchard, Aimee; Kumar, Vinita (Box 9)
  - EXP 009 B F'89 Changing Youth in a Changing Society, 1989; UA044.002.009.00003; Peterson, Scott; Rafofsky, Shari (Box 9)
  - EXP 009 C F'89 Friendship in Perspective, 1989; UA044.002.009.00004; Regnante, Keith; DeMaria, Christine (Box 9)
  - EXP 009 D F'89 Love and Marriage?, 1989; UA044.002.009.00005; Rosen, Brian; Salvatore, Lara (Box 9)
  - EXP 009 E F'89 The Contemporary Athlete, 1989; UA044.002.009.00006; Turner, Scott; Tamir, Mira (Box 9)
  - EXP 009 F F'89 American Ethics, 1989; UA044.002.009.00007; Difiore, Carrie; Yang, Ken (Box 9)
  - EXP 009 F F'89 Values and Beliefs, 1989; UA044.002.009.00008; Sancho, Robert; Shaw, Leslie (Box 9)
  - Explorations, 1991 -- 2000; UA044.002.033 (Box 33)
    Appraisal